snap15.com 2011-01-12

# Privacy :: Snap15

**Scope**

Snap15.com ("Snap15") is a service provided by Status Holiday Pvt. Ltd. We acknowledge and respect your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy describes all aspects relating to gathering information while you're visiting Snap15.  
By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms & Conditions in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective seven (7) days after being posted on the website.

**Data Collection**

You may visit Snap15.com at any time without intentionally revealing any personal information about yourself. However, when you visit our website, we may collect and store your computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Snap15, advertisement data, IP address and standard web log information and information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data.  
For you to actively participate in Snap15 we do need some of your personal information. Once you provide us with your required personal information, you are no longer anonymous. In providing us with your personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of such information on our servers.  
When you register on Snap15, we will collect the following required information: email address, first and last name, date of birth, and password; all transactional information based on your activities on Snap15; shipping, billing and other information relating to any purchase or shipping; any correspondence sent to us; financial information, such as your credit card information; and other supplemental information from third parties. 

**Use of Data**

Our purpose for collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, efficient, and customized experience. By signing up, you agree that we may use your personal information to: provide the services and customer support you request; resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms & Conditions; customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising; inform you about our services, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotions; and compare information and verify it with third parties for accuracy. 

**Disclosure of Personal Data**

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. This information will be disclosed under applicable laws and regulations.  
We may also share your personal information with third parties assisting our business operations under contract, including but not limited to fraud investigations and debt collection, with law enforcement or other governmental officials if required by law, and with other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. 

**Your Information on Snap15**

Once you have been approved as a registered user with Snap15, you will be required to choose a user name. This user name will be displayed throughout Snap15 and therefore provided to the public. Unless you associate your user name with your personal information, other users will not be able to personally identify your activities on Snap15.  
When visiting Snap15 from a public or shared computer, certain information about you, such as your user name, may also be visible to others who may use that computer after your use. 

**Access, Review and Change of Personal Data**

You can access, review and change most of your personal information by logging on to Snap15 at any time. However, some of your personal information can only be changed by contacting our Customer Service. You are required to promptly update your personal information if changes occur or information is inaccurate. 

**Closing Your Account**

Upon closing your account, Snap15 will remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms & Conditions, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law. 

**Use of Cookies at our Website**

Snap15 uses so-called "cookies", which are files that are stored on your computer that can be retrieved to assist in customizing your experience with the online service. The information saved supports the functionality of the site, for example, by keeping track of your visual preferences or controlling the frequency of "pop-up" windows. You are free to prevent cookies from being saved on your hard drive by adjusting the corresponding settings in your browser. However, turning off these settings may result in limited functionality. 

**Security Measures**

Your Snap15 account and profile and the information contained therein are password protected. Please note that you are not permitted to provide your password to anyone else. Snap15 will never ask for your password in e-mail or over the phone. Please remember to log out of your account and to close your Internet browser window when you leave the Snap15 site; this is especially important if you use a PC in public locations. We assume no liability for the abuse of login data and passwords used.  
Snap15 treats data as an asset that must be highly protected. We use security measures to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

**Protection from Web Crawlers or Spam**

Snap15 assures you that we will use your e-mail address with your express consent only for the purposes stated in the Terms & Conditions. We will not rent or sell your e-mail address to third parties, and we will prevent your e-mail address from being recorded by "web crawlers" or "web spiders" to the best of our ability. If you believe that your e-mail address has been recorded in this way, please email us at support@Snap15.com immediately. 

**General**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the new Privacy Policy on Snap15. All amended terms automatically take effect 10 days after they are initially posted on the site. 

**Questions?**

If you have a privacy question about Snap15, please email us at **support@Snap15.com**
